Guide to the Yale Summer and Special Programs Records Concerning the American Economic Association Summer Minority Program
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Summer and Special Programs records concerning the American Economic Association Summer Minority Program
1975-1982
RU 721
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.75
(4 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, program information, student evaluations, financial papers, and subject files of the Yale Summer and Special Programs documenting the activities and operations of the American Economic Association Summer Minority Program at Yale, which ended in 1982.
Yale Summer and Special Programs
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 15-B (YRG 15-B), Records of specific Yale summer and special programs.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, program information, student evaluations, financial papers, and subject files of the Yale Summer and Special Programs documenting the activities and operations of the American Economic Association Summer Minority Program at Yale, which ended in 1982.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by subject.
Minorities -- Education (Higher); University extension; American Economic Association; Yale Summer and Special Programs; Yale University -- Administration
- Records concerning the American Economic Association Summer Minority Program, 1975-1982; Accession 1984-A-029
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2018.
  - Academic Program (Box 1, Folder 1 - 2)
    - Friday Afternoon Seminars, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3 - 4)
    - Wednesday Evening Seminars, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 5 - 6)
  - Advertising, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7 - 8)
    - Basic Letters, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Colleges - Mailing Lists, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 10 - 11)
    - Expenses, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Internal Letters, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Posters, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Publicity, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Tear sheets, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Application, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 17 - 18)
    - Materials, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 19 - 20)
  - Classroom Evaluations, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Classroom Information, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 22 - 23)
  - Classroom Materials, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 25 - 29)
  - Expenses, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 31 - 33)
  - Faculty and Staff, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 34 - 36)
  - Federal Reserve Bank, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 37 - 38)
  - Final Exams, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Final Luncheon, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Final Report, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 41 - 42)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Forms, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Information
    - For Students, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 46 - 47)
    - Packet, orientation, for AEA Summer minority Students, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Minority Recruitment, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Orientation Packet, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 50 - 51)
  - Program Evaluations, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 52 - 54)
  - Questionnaires for 1981-1982, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 55 - 56)
  - Registration - Orientation, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Staff Meetings, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Statistics, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 59 - 61)
  - Students
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Lists, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 63 - 64)
      - Academic, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 65)
      - Class, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 66)
      - Non-Academic, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Orientation packet, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Stipend Checks, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 69 - 70)
  - Transcripts, Requests for, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Travel, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 72 - 74)